https://www.profitspi.com/stock/view.aspx?vc=privacy

View pricing
HomeBacktestingScreeningChartsPatternsWatch ListsExchangesUpload DataDaily EmailStrategy LibraryScreen LibraryChart LibraryPattern Library
Home : Privacy Policy
Profitspi Privacy PolicyWhat This Privacy Policy Covers This Privacy Policy covers Profitspi's treatment of personally identifiable information that Profitspi collects when you are on the Profitspi site, and when you use Profitspi's services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Profitspi does not own or control, or to people that Profitspi does not employ or manage.Information Collection and UseProfitspi collects personally identifiable information when you sign up for a Profitspi account and when you visit Profitspi pages. When you register with Profitspi, we ask for your email address. We require your email address so that we can send a confirmation email when you sign up. Also, if you forget your password we need to know your email address so that Profitspi can identify you and send you another one. Once you register with Profitspi and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Profitspi also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Profitspi cookie information and each page you have requested.Information Sharing and DisclosureProfitspi will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone. Profitspi will only send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:
we have your consent to share the information;
we respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
we find that your actions on our web sites violate the Profitspi Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. CookiesProfitspi may set and access Profitspi cookies on your computer. Profitspi allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Profitspi's cookies.Specific information regarding Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and PreferencesProfitspi gives you the ability to edit your account information and preferences at any time. You may request deletion of your Profitspi account by sending a message using the contact us page.User Ids not accessed in more than 6 monthsTo ensure that the information you store on Profitspi is always available to you, you must access the Profitspi service at least once every 6 months. Profitspi may periodically delete information stored on its servers if that information has not been accessed in 6 months. This does not apply if you are a current Subscriber.SecurityYour Profitspi Account Information is password-protected for your privacy and security. In certain areas Profitspi uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions.Changes to this Privacy PolicyProfitspi may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages. You agree that such posting will constitute sufficient and adequate notice to you of the changes. You agree that your continued use of Profitspi's products or services after such amendment will constitute your acceptance of and agreement to be bound by the modified policy.
Our services
Pricing
Backtesting and screening API
Company information
About us
Contact us
Terms of service
Privacy policy
© 2020 Profitspi Pte Ltd.
All data is end-of-day.
